VAGELIS KOSMIADIS

CONTACT



+30 6984430394



✓ vageliskosmiadis@gmail.com



https://portfolio-site-dusky-alpha.vercel.app/

PROFILE SUMMARY

Undergraduate in last year of Senior High School participating in National Exams aiming to pursue Computer Science Studies at Aristotle University of Thessaloniki. Almost 4 years of experience as a selftaught Front-End Web Developer. Excited and disciplined to work in the tech industry, eager to learn and acquire new skills.

EDUCATION

2022-now

4TH SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL OF **STAVROUPOLI**

- Computer Science and Economics Major
- Participating in the National Exams (Panellinies) in order to pursue Computer Science Studies.

SKILLS

Web Development (HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React.js, TailwindCSS, Redux, Typescript

Backend Development (Node.js, Express.js)

Version Control System (Git, Github) Database (MongoDB) Experience in Docker, Python, Java **Problem Solving Skills** Keenness in learning new skills

LANGUAGES

- Greek Native Speaker
- English Written and Oral Fluency (B2 Certificate holder -High Pass)
- German Basics (Knowledge acquired from school classes)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tiler's Assistant & Social Media JUNE 2024--AUGUST 2024 Manager

- Basic assistance services for a local tiler.
- Social Media Management and Website Creation, for a local furniture restoration shop, bringing over 1m+ views in all social media platforms

Truck Repair Workshop Assistant JUNE 2023-JULY 2023

Basic assistance services in a truck repairing workshop